

# Andrea Piombo

Date of birth: 03/02/2004 Residence: Milan (MI) Nationality: Italian Driving license: B

### **CONTACTS**

Email: contact@piomboandrea.net

Phone: (+39) 3273719655 Website: piomboandrea.net

#### **PROFILE**

I've been a student at Politecnico di Milano in the field of biomedical engineering but I've switched to a more practice-oriented course at ITS Nuove Tecnologie della Vita. I've graduated in the field of Electrotechnics with a specialization on medical equipement. I give my best while working in team both as team leader and as member. One of my main hobbies is coding and I have some experience with python, javascript, html & css.

### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

10/2024 – CURRENT | Milan, Italy
V EQF level Degree in Technology & Digital Healthcare

ITS Ospedale San Raffaele

Website: fondazionebiotecnologie.it

09/2018 - 06/2023 | Milan, Italy

Electrotechnical diploma with electromedical training

IIS Luigi Galvani

Website: <u>iisgalvanimi.edu.it</u> | Final grade: 98/100

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

09/2022 - CURRENT | Northern Italy

Computer technician for Federazione Italiana Scherma

Management of competitions [creation, execution, conclusion] and upload of results in real time

Acquired skills:

- Resources, space and time management
- Work under pressure and with direct contact to the public

02/2022 – 06/2022 | Lombardy, Italy Electromedical technician for ANTEV

Electrical safety checks on medical devices and wiring circuits

### LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE: italian
Other language: english (B2)

# **DIGITAL SKILLS**

SOFTWARE

Mastery of the Office package | Fair knowledge of AutoCAD Good knowledge of the TiPlan program (Bticino)

HARDWARE

Good electrical knowledge and skills | Discrete Siemens PLC programming Good execution of the wiring of LV electrical systems Familiarity with various medical devices (especially DaVinci Robotic Surgical Systems)

# **HOBBIES AND INTERESTS**

Programming

Link: github.com/Piombacciaio

Didactics

Course for the use and basic maintenance of the Surgery System "DaVinci" robotics and other medical equipment at IIS L. Galvani.

Cultural activities

Music, Reading, Movies, Travels

Sports

Former competitive fencer, gym

### **VOLUNTEERING**

03/2023 - CURRENT | Milan, Italy

Blood donor with Associazione Amici del Policlinico